Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 83, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 83, Folder 41)
  - Item 2: British Transport, Publication (Box 83, Folder 41)
    Author: Labour Party
- Box: 83, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 83, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Analysis of Rail and Truck Statistics as "Economic Indicators, Publication (Box 83, Folder 42)
- Box: 83, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 83, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: The Transportation System of Our Nation, 1962; Publication (Box 83, Folder 43)
    Notes: April 5, 1962
- Box: 83, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 83, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: All the Pirates are Not Dead, Publication (Box 83, Folder 44)
  - Item 2: Jurisdictional Conflicts and the Coordination of Transportation, 1960; Publication (Box 83, Folder 44)
    Author: U.S. Interstate Commerce Commission
  - Item 3: "Petty" Discrimination in Transport Regulation, Publication (Box 83, Folder 44)
    Author: Federation for Railway Progress
- Box: 83, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 83, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Transit Strike Highlights, 1967; Publication (Box 83, Folder 45)
    Author: Tri-State Transportation Commission
    Notes: January 1967
  - Item 2: Metropolitan Mobility, 1965; Publication (Box 83, Folder 45)
    Author: City Planning Commission
- Box: 83, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 83, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Comparitive Transportation Statistics, 1966; Publication (Box 83, Folder 46)
- Box: 84, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Allowances for Employee Expenses, 1972; Publication (Box 84, Folder 1)
    Notes: August 1972
  - Item 2: Current Business Car Allowances, Controls, and Practices, Publication (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Box: 84, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Basic Data on the Economy of Trinidad and Tobago, 1965; Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Box: 84, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: History and Regulation of Trailer-on-Flatcar Movement, 1966; Publication (Box 84, Folder 3)
    Author: Josephine Ayre
    Notes: January 19, 1966
- Box: 84, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: How Bootleg Trucking Hurts You, Publication (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Box: 84, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Out of Your Pocket, Publication (Box 84, Folder 5)
    Author: Darel McConkey
  - Item 2: The Cartel System, Publication (Box 84, Folder 5)
    Author: James S. Allen
  - Item 3: International Cartels and World Peace, 1944; Publication (Box 84, Folder 5)
    Author: Post War World Council
  - Item 4: Cartels or Free Enterprise?, Publication (Box 84, Folder 5)
    Author: Thurman W. Arnold
  - Item 5: NAM Looks at Cartels, Publication (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Box: 84, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Regulation by Visible Public and Invisible Private Government, Publication (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Box: 84, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Opinion, Publication (Box 84, Folder 7)
    Author: American Trucking Associations
- Box: 84, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Public Policy Toward Competition, 1962; Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: The Federal Antitrust Laws, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    Author: Jerrold G. Van Cise
- Box: 84, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Tuberculoses Labor and Management, 1944; Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    Author: William Arkwright Doppler
- Box: 84, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Turkey, 1961; Publication (Box 84, Folder 10)
    Notes: July 1961
- Box: 84, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Report of the Committee on Wages and Conditions of Service of Government Unestablished Employees, 1962; Publication (Box 84, Folder 11)
    Author: Uganda Protectorate
  - Item 2: Wages Increase Claim, 1966; Publication (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Box: 84, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Capital Development Needs of the Less Developed Countries, Publication (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Student Conference on United States Affairs, 1964; Publication (Box 84, Folder 12)
    Author: U.S. Military Academy
    Notes: December 2-5, 1964
  - Item 3: Reserves and Reservations, Publication (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Box: 84, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Selected Economic Data for the Less Developed Countries, 1966; Publication (Box 84, Folder 13)
    Author: U.S. Agency for International Development
- Box: 84, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Relief of Destitute Unemployed, 1915; Publication (Box 84, Folder 14)
    Author: California Commission of Immigration and Housing
    Notes: June 25, 1915
  - Item 2: Statutes of the International Asociation, Publication (Box 84, Folder 14)
    Author: International Association on Unemployment
    Language: English; German; French.
  - Item 3: Unemployment, 1915; Publication (Box 84, Folder 14)
    Author: Walter E. Kruesi
  - Item 4: Speech, 1914; Publication (Box 84, Folder 14)
    Author: National Bureau of Employment
    Notes: May 1, 1914
  - Item 5: Report of Committee on Employment, 1936; Publication (Box 84, Folder 14)
    Notes: November 1936
  - Item 6: Mayor's Sub-Committee on Unemployment Among Women, 1915; Publication (Box 84, Folder 14)
    Author: Mayor's Sub-Committee on Unemployment Among Women
  - Item 7: Unemployment, 1932; Publication (Box 84, Folder 14)
    Author: Charles G. Ross
- Box: 84, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Closing of the Studebaker Plant, 1964; Publication (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Sub-Employment in the Slums of Boston, Publication (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Sub-Employment in the Slums of Phoenix, Publication (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Sub-Employment in the Slums of Philadelphia, Publication (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Sub-Employment in the Slums of San Antonio, Publication (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Sub-Employment in the Slums of Los Angeles, Publication (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Sub-Employment in the Slums of Oakland, Publication (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Sub-Employment in the Slums of New Orleans, Publication (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Sub-Employment in the Slums of Cleveland, Publication (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Sub-Employment in the Slums of New York, Publication (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: New Dimensions in Manpower, Publication (Box 84, Folder 15)
    Author: Chicago Committee on Urban Opportunity
- Box: 84, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Reasons for Alabama's Unemployed, 1965; Publication (Box 84, Folder 16)
    Author: Alabama Department of Industrial Relations
- Box: 84, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Unemployment in Antigua, 1952; Publication (Box 84, Folder 17)
    Author: Simon Rottenberg, Nora Siffleet
- Box: 84, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Structural Unemployment, 1962; Publication (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Employment, Publication (Box 84, Folder 18)
    Author: John B. Wood
- Box: 84, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Report on Unemployment, 1914; Publication (Box 84, Folder 19)
    Author: Hiram W. Johnson
    Notes: December 9, 1914
- Box: 84, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Facts About the Unemployed, 1971; Publication (Box 84, Folder 20)
    Author: Canada Labour Division
    Notes: September 1971
  - Item 2: Unemployment in Ontario, 1961; Publication (Box 84, Folder 20)
    Author: Ontario Federation of Labour
    Notes: March 15, 1961
  - Item 3: Ontario Commission on Unemployment, 1915; Publication (Box 84, Folder 20)
    Author: Ontario Legislative Assembly
    Notes: July 20, 1915
- Box: 84, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Story of the Detroit Times, Publication (Box 84, Folder 21)
    Author: Louis A. Ferman
- Box: 84, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Problems of Merseyside, Publication (Box 84, Folder 22)
    Author: Great Britain Department of Economic Affairs
  - Item 2: Duration of Unemployment on the Register of Wholly Unemployed, Publication (Box 84, Folder 22)
    Author: R.F. Fowler
  - Item 3: Employment and Unemployment in the Hull Region, 1964; Publication (Box 84, Folder 22)
    Author: Eric W. Evans, Keith Hartley
  - Item 4: Unemployment, Publication (Box 84, Folder 22)
    Author: Peter Hampton
  - Item 5: Managerial Mobility and Redundancy, Publication (Box 84, Folder 22)
- Box: 84, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Report, 1963; Publication (Box 84, Folder 23)
    Author: Hawaii Department of Labor and Industrial Relations
- Box: 84, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Educational Attainment of Regular and TEC Claimants, 1966; Publication (Box 84, Folder 24)
    Author: Illinois Department of Labor
  - Item 2: Employment, 1963; Publication (Box 84, Folder 24)
    Author: Governor's Committee on Unemployment
  - Item 3: How People React to a Decline in Jobs, 1954; Publication (Box 84, Folder 24)
    Notes: April 1954
- Box: 84, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Role of Unemployment Insurance in National Manpower Policies, Publication (Box 84, Folder 25)
    Author: Louise Levine
  - Item 2: The Adequacy of the Benefit Amount in Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 84, Folder 25)
    Author: Joseph M. Becker
  - Item 3: Unemployment Compensation, 1937; Publication (Box 84, Folder 25)
    Author: U.S. Social Security Board
    Notes: September 1937
  - Item 4: Unemployment Insurance, 1948; Publication (Box 84, Folder 25)
    Author: A.D. Watson
  - Item 5: The Role of Unemployment Compensation in Maintaining Family Income and Expenditure in an Area of Critical Unemployment, 1951; Publication (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: State Unemployment Insurance Laws, 1950; Publication (Box 84, Folder 25)
    Notes: January 1, 1950
  - Item 7: Company Plans for Unemployment Reserves, 1932; Publication (Box 84, Folder 25)
    Notes: September 1932
  - Item 8: Nonprofit Employment, Publication (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Item 9: Unemployment Insurance and Agricultural Labor in the United States, 1949; Publication (Box 84, Folder 25)
    Author: Abraham Libove
  - Item 10: Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Item 11: British Experience with Unemployment Insurance: Part One, Publication (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Item 12: British Experience with Unemployment Insurance: Part Two, Publication (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Item 13: British Experience with Unemployment Insurance: Part Five, Publication (Box 84, Folder 25)
- Box: 84, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Act, 1966; Publication (Box 84, Folder 26)
- Box: 84, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Insurance Claimants with Benefit Years, 1969; Publication (Box 84, Folder 27)
    Notes: December 1969
  - Item 2: Unemployment Insurance Beneficiaries, Publication (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Alabama Unemployment Compensation Law, Publication (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: Characteristics of the Labor Market in Alabama Related to the Administration of Unemployment Compensation, 1937; Publication (Box 84, Folder 27)
    Author: Burton R. Morley
- Box: 84, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Insurance Benefit Entitlement Study, 1968; Publication (Box 84, Folder 28)
- Box: 84, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Alaska Administrative Code, Publication (Box 84, Folder 29)
    Author: Alaska Department of Labor
  - Item 2: Employment Security Program Activities, Publication (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: The Benefit Formeula Provisions of Unemployment Insurance in Alaska, 1959; Publication (Box 84, Folder 29)
    Author: Gerald C. Stromberg
  - Item 4: Rural and Urban Unemployment Insurance Claimants, Publication (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Unemployment Insurance Claimants, Publication (Box 84, Folder 29)
- Box: 84, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Employment Security Law, 1966; Publication (Box 84, Folder 30)
    Author: Arizona Employment Security Commission
  - Item 2: Employment Security Law, 1962; Publication (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Eligibility on Lag-Period Earnings, 1961; Publication (Box 84, Folder 30)
    Notes: January 1961
  - Item 4: The Widening Gap, 1962; Publication (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: Average Weekly Wage, Publication (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: Employment Security Law, 1971; Publication (Box 84, Folder 30)
    Notes: August 1971
- Box: 84, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 84, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: The Point of No Return, 1963; Publication (Box 84, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Voluntary Contributions, 1968; Publication (Box 84, Folder 31)
    Notes: December 1968
- Box: 84, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 84, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Employment Security Commission of Arizona, 1966; Publication (Box 84, Folder 32)
    Author: Arizona Unemployment Compensation Division
- Box: 85, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Workers Who Do Not File Claims for Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 85, Folder 1)
    Author: Arkansas Employment Security Division
- Box: 85, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Insurance in Austria, 1932; Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
    Author: Mollie Ray Carroll
- Box: 85, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Unemployment and Unemployment Insurance and its Administration, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Cumulative Report on Unemployment Insurance and its Administration, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: California's Employment Security System, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: California's Employment Security System, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Joint Interim Legislative Unemployment Insurance Committee, 1968; Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Box: 85, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Financial Prospects for the California Unemployment Insurance Program, 1961; Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Box: 85, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    Author: Canada Unemployment Insurance Commission
  - Item 2: Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Information for Employers on Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Unemployment Insurance Act, 1969; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Unemployment Insurance Act, 1949; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: An Act, 1935; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    Author: Canada House of Commons
    Notes: March 12, 1935
  - Item 7: Unemployment Insurance in the 70s, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Box: 85, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Report of the Connecticut Governor's Committee on Unemployment Compensation, 1950; Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
    Author: Connecticut Governor's Committee on Unemployment Compensation
    Notes: May 10, 1950
- Box: 85, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Compensation Law, 1951; Publication (Box 85, Folder 7)
    Author: Delaware Unemployment Compensation Commission
- Box: 85, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Among Current and Potential Initial Claimants, 1959; Publication (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Box: 85, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Delayed Filing for Unemployment Benefits in Ohio, Publication (Box 85, Folder 9)
    Author: Ohio Division of Research and Statistics
- Box: 85, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Labor Market Experience of UI Exhaustees, Publication (Box 85, Folder 10)
    Author: Vermont Unemployment Compensation Commission
  - Item 2: Unemployment Compensation, 1957; Publication (Box 85, Folder 10)
    Author: Nevada Employment Security Laws
- Box: 85, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Insurance Beneficiaries, 1965; Publication (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Comparitive Analysis of Claimants and Exhaustees, Publication (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Characteristics of Alabama's Exhaustees, Publication (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Box: 85, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: What Happens to the Jobless When Unemployment Insurance Expires?, 1950; Publication (Box 85, Folder 12)
    Notes: May 1950
- Box: 85, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Post Exhaustion Labor, Publication (Box 85, Folder 13)
- Box: 85, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Claims Exhaustions in Indiana, 1957; Publication (Box 85, Folder 14)
    Author: Gene S. Booker
    Notes: April - September 1957
- Box: 85, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Exhaustion Experience and Labor Force Status of the Long-Term Unemployed in Ohio, Publication (Box 85, Folder 15)
- Box: 85, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Post-Exhaustion Labor Force Status of TEUC Claimants in Tennessee, 1965; Publication (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Claimant Exhaustee Characteristics, Publication (Box 85, Folder 16)
- Box: 85, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Personal and Economic Characteristics of Florida Claimants, 1962; Publication (Box 85, Folder 17)
    Author: Florida Industrial Commission
  - Item 2: Unemployment Compensation, 1960; Publication (Box 85, Folder 17)
    Notes: January 1, 1960
  - Item 3: Request Wage Reporting and the Florida Unemployment Benefit Structure, Publication (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: The Florida Unemployment Compensation Law, 1962; Publication (Box 85, Folder 17)
    Notes: January 1, 1962
- Box: 85, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The National Employment Fund, 1965; Publication (Box 85, Folder 18)
    Author: Ambassade de France
- Box: 85, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Report of the Great Britain National Insurance Advisory Committee, 1968; Publication (Box 85, Folder 19)
    Author: Great Britain National Insurance Advisory Committee
  - Item 2: Redundancy Payments Act, Publication (Box 85, Folder 19)
    Author: Great Britain Labour Research Department
- Box: 85, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Hawaii's Unemployed, Publication (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Disqualified Claimants Among Hawaii's Insured Unemployed, Publication (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Unemployment Insurance in Hawaii, Publication (Box 85, Folder 20)
- Box: 85, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Long-Range Unemployment Insurance Financing in Hawaii, 1959; Publication (Box 85, Folder 21)
    Notes: October 1959
- Box: 85, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Insurance Financing and Benefit Costs in Idaho, 1960; Publication (Box 85, Folder 22)
    Author: Idaho Employment Security Agency
- Box: 85, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Effects of an Increase in the Tax Base for Unemployment Compensation in Illinois, 1967; Publication (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: The Unemployment Compensation Act, 1967; Publication (Box 85, Folder 23)
    Notes: September 7, 1967
  - Item 3: Employed Workers Covered by the Illinois Unemployment Compensation Act, Publication (Box 85, Folder 23)
    Author: Illinois State Employment Service
  - Item 4: Unemployment Compensation in Illinois, Publication (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: The Facts About Unemployment Compensation, Publication (Box 85, Folder 23)
    Author: Illinois Bureau of Employment Security
  - Item 6: The Facts About Unemployment Compensation, Publication (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Item 7: Extension of Unemployment Compensation, 1968; Publication (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Item 8: A Guide to the Illinois Unemployment Compensation Act, Publication (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Item 9: A Guide to the Illinois Unemployment Compensation Act, Publication (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: The Unemployment Compensation Act, 1967; Publication (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Item 11: The Unemployment Compensation Act, 1951; Publication (Box 85, Folder 23)
    Notes: July 1, 1951
- Box: 85, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Effects of an Increase in the Tax Base for Unemployment Compensation in Illinois, 1967; Publication (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Effects of an Increase in the Tax Base for Unemployment Compensation in Illinois, 1967; Publication (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: The Illinois Unemployment Trust Fund, 1965; Publication (Box 85, Folder 24)
- Box: 85, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Insured Unemployed, 1960; Publication (Box 85, Folder 25)
    Author: Indiana Employment Security Division
  - Item 2: Indiana Employment Security Act, 1965; Publication (Box 85, Folder 25)
    Author: Indiana Employment Security Board
  - Item 3: History of Indiana Employment Security Legislation, 1953; Publication (Box 85, Folder 25)
    Notes: November 1953
- Box: 85, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Financing Unemployment Insurance Benefits in Indiana, Publication (Box 85, Folder 26)
    Author: John A. Delehanty
  - Item 2: Some Significant Statistics About Unemployment Insurance in Indiana, 1963; Publication (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Deficit Experience Accounts and Their Part in Financing Unemployment Insurance Benefits, 1960; Publication (Box 85, Folder 26)
    Notes: February 1960
  - Item 4: Deficit Experience Accounts and Their Part in Financing Unemployment Insurance Benefits, 1962; Publication (Box 85, Folder 26)
- Box: 85, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The Insured Unemployed, 1963; Publication (Box 85, Folder 27)
    Notes: April 1963
- Box: 85, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Convention on Unemployment Insurance, 1962; Publication (Box 85, Folder 28)
    Author: Great Britain Foreign Office
- Box: 85, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 85, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Insurance Legislative Planning, 1968; Publication (Box 85, Folder 29)
    Author: Kansas Department of Labor
- Box: 86, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Financing Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    Author: Kentucky Department of Economic Security
- Box: 86, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Employment, Wages, Contributions, 1965; Publication (Box 86, Folder 2)
    Author: Maine Employment Security Commission
  - Item 2: Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Box: 86, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Who are the Unemployed?, Publication (Box 86, Folder 3)
    Author: New Hampshire Division of Employment Security
- Box: 86, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Maryland Story on Employment Security, Publication (Box 86, Folder 4)
    Author: Maryland Department of Employment Security
  - Item 2: Regulations of the Maryland Department of Employment Security, 1962; Publication (Box 86, Folder 4)
    Notes: December 6, 1962
  - Item 3: Unemployment Insurance Policy, Publication (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Box: 86, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Massachusetts Employment Security Law, 1964; Publication (Box 86, Folder 5)
    Author: Massachusetts State Advisory Council
  - Item 2: Massachusetts Employment Security Law, 1967; Publication (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Report, 1923; Publication (Box 86, Folder 5)
    Author: Wright & Potter Printing Co.
    Notes: February 9, 1923
  - Item 4: Unemployment Compensation Commission, 1939; Publication (Box 86, Folder 5)
    Notes: January 9, 1939
  - Item 5: Report, 1949; Publication (Box 86, Folder 5)